<resources>
    <!--
    happiro TEST = key_id, key_secret
    rzp_test_9Nt3b3grKDXHcq,
    bamD1Ask5UuET8l1mZacKwfI

    Happiro live = key_id,key_secret
rzp_live_JHkGoJA11Bv4sg,nmaLPRn9BPu9LcNLrCBgi1Wt
     -->
    <string name="razerKeyTest">rzp_test_9Nt3b3grKDXHcq</string>
    <string name="razerKey">rzp_live_JHkGoJA11Bv4sg</string>
    <string name="app_name">Happiroo</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="refer_amp_earn"><![CDATA[Refer & Earn]]></string>
    <string name="about_mclap">About Happiroo</string>
    <string name="share_app">Share App</string>
    <string name="rate_mclap">Rate Happiroo</string>
    <string name="terms_amp_conditions"><![CDATA[Terms & Conditions]]></string>
    <string name="frequently_asked_questions">Frequently Asked Questions</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="my_profile">My Profile</string>
    <string name="title">title</string>
    <string name="select_a_service">Select a service</string>
    <string name="how_we_do">How we do</string>
    <string name="rate_cards">Rate Cards</string>
    <string name="m_clap_assurance">Happiroo Assurance</string>
    <string name="skilled_and_verified_professionals_n_n_u20b95000_damage_cover_on_every_booking">Skilled and verified professionals\n\n₹5000 damage cover on every booking</string>
    <string name="address_details">Address Details</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="change">Change</string>
    <string name="address_type">Address Type</string>
    <string name="update_now">Update Now</string>
    <string name="flat_building_street">Flat / Building / Street</string>
    <string name="mobile_number">Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="select_address">Select Address</string>
    <string name="add_a_new_address">Add a new address</string>
    <string name="my_saved_addresses">My Saved Addresses</string>
    <string name="skip_for_now">Skip for now</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="add_review">Add Review</string>
    <string name="booking_details">Booking Details</string>
    <string name="service_location">Service Location</string>
    <string name="timing">Timing</string>
    <string name="invoice">Invoice</string>
    <string name="amount_paid">Amount Paid</string>
    <string name="service_start_otp">Service start OTP</string>
    <string name="my_cart">My Cart</string>
    <string name="color_tray_wallet">Wallet</string>
    <string name="you_used">You used</string>
    <string name="apply_promo_code">Apply promo code</string>
    <string name="continue_to_pay">Continue to pay</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="payment_options">Payment Options</string>
    <string name="service_slot">Service Slot</string>
    <string name="services">Services</string>
    <string name="confirm_booking">Confirm Booking</string>
    <string name="view_detail">View Detail</string>
    <string name="need_help">Need Help?</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="state">State</string>
    <string name="coutry">Country</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_mclap">Welcome to Happiroo</string>
    <string name="add_to_cart">Add to cart</string>
    <string name="service_description_amp_detail"><![CDATA[Service Description & Detail]]></string>
    <string name="what_s_included">What\'s included?</string>
    <string name="what_s_excluded">What\'s excluded?</string>
    <string name="brand_s_and_equipment_used">Brand(s) and Equipment Used</string>
    <string name="additional_details">Additional Details</string>
    <string name="lemend_assurance">Happiroo Assurance</string>
    <string name="customer_ratings_amp_reviews"><![CDATA[Customer Ratings & Reviews]]></string>
    <string name="add_your_rating">Add your rating</string>
    <string name="damage_cover_on_every_booking">Skilled and verified professionals\n\n₹5000 damage cover on every booking</string>
    <string name="select_quantity">Select Quantity</string>
    <string name="total_amount">Total Amount</string>
    <string name="item_description">Description</string>
    <string name="no_ratings_for_this_product">No ratings for this product</string>
    <string name="five_reviews">60 Reviews</string>
    <string name="rate_product">Rate Product</string>
    <string name="ratings_amp_reviews">Ratings and Review</string>

    <string name="product_details">1.Support A2DP,AVRCP, Handsfree profile,FM radio
2.With FM function, can search radio station broadcast automatically
    </string>
    <string name="my_orders">My Orders</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="items">Items</string>
    <string name="favourite_products">Favourite Products</string>
    <string name="channel_id">channel_1</string>
    <string name="tnc">"Welcome to Happiroo.\nYou may use our services through our website www.Happiroo.in (“Website”) or our mobile application. Our App have been created to provide information about our company and services to the visitors and user of services, whether accessible to you via web, mobile App or other platform (our services, together with the Site, are the \"Services\") For the purpose of these Terms of Use, the term 'Happiroo' or 'Us' or 'We' refers to Happiroo. The term 'You' refers to the user or viewer of our App. When You use any of the Services provided by Us, including but not limited to, Electrical, Plumbing,  Laundry, etc, you will be subject to the rules, guidelines, policies, terms, and conditions applicable to such service, and they shall be deemed to be incorporated into this Terms of Use and shall be considered as part and parcel of these Terms of Use.\n As long as you comply with these Terms of Use, We grant you a personal, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited privilege to enter and use our platforms.\nIn the event of a conflict or inconsistency between any provision of the terms and conditions mentioned herein with those of the particular service, the provisions of the terms and conditions applicable to such specific Services shall prevail. Acceptance of Terms \n⦁\tThese Terms of Use set forth legally binding terms for your use of our Platforms. By using, visit, accessing our platforms, you agree to be bound by this Terms of Use, whether you are a “Visitor” (which means that you simply browse our Platforms) or you are a “Subscriber” (which means that you have registered with Happiroo as a user). If you do not accept the Terms of Use, you should leave the Website and/or  App and discontinue use of the Service immediately. \n⦁\tWe may modify these Terms from time to time, and such modification shall be effective upon its posting on our platforms. You agree to be bound by any modification to this Agreement when you use our Website and App after any such modification is posted; it is therefore important that you review the Terms of Use regularly. General Registration Requirements \n⦁\tIn consideration of your use of our platforms, you represent that you are of legal age (18 years and above) to form a binding contract and are not a person barred from receiving services under any law in force in India or other applicable jurisdiction. You also agree to: \n⦁\tprovide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself while registering on our Website and  App to avail the Services. \n⦁\tmaintain and promptly update your Registration Data to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. \n⦁\tIf you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, or we have reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, We reserve the right to suspend or terminate your account and refuse any and all current or future use of our Website and  App(or any portion thereof) at any time. Happiroo will not be liable for any act or omission arising from the inaccurate information provided by You to Us. \n⦁\tYou may access our Website and  App as available: \n⦁\tfor your information and personal use; \n⦁\tas intended through the normal functionality of Happiroo. \n⦁\tYou will be required to enter a valid phone number while registering on our Website and  App as a subscriber. By registering your phone number with us, you consent to be contacted by us via phone calls and/or SMS notifications, in case of any subscription/service updates. If we do so, each communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to \"opt-out\" of receiving future communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below. If you are registered with the DND National registry you may not receive any promotional messages from us. Subscriber Account, Password and Security \n⦁\tIf you register on Happiroo, you will be required to choose a password and user name. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account information, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account. You agree to: \n⦁\timmediately notify Happiroo of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, and \n⦁\tensure that you log out from your account at the end of each session; \n⦁\tnever use any other Subscriber’s account without prior authorization from Happiroo \n⦁\tHappiroo will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this Agreement. User Information \n⦁\tHappiroo’s unique business model provides You with location based service providers in a short span of time. To facilitate this, You hereby authorise Happiroo to use the location based information provided by any of the telecommunication companies when You use the mobile phone to make a booking. The location based information will be used only to facilitate and improve services for You. \n⦁\tIf You use the Website or the App, You agree that information about Your use of the Happiroo Website and  App through Your mobile telecommunication device may be communicated to us, and we may obtain information about Your mobile carrier, Your mobile device, or Your physical location. By accessing the  App or Website using a mobile telecommunication device, You represent that to the extent You import any of Your Happiroo data to Your mobile telecommunication device that You have authority to share the transferred data with Your mobile carrier or other access provider. In the event You change or deactivate Your mobile account, You must promptly update Your Happiroo account information to ensure that Your messages are not sent to the person that acquires Your old number and failure to do so is Your responsibility. You acknowledge that You are responsible for all charges and necessary permissions related to accessing the  App through Your mobile access provider. Therefore, You should check with Your provider to find out if our Website and  App are available and the terms for these services for Your specific mobile devices. \n⦁\tHappiroo reserves the right to collect user data including name, contact information and other details to facilitate the Services or use of its  App to avail Services. \n⦁\tCompilation of user accounts and user accounts bearing contact number and e-mail addresses are owned by Happiroo. \n⦁\tIn the case where the system is unable to establish unique identity of the user against a valid mobile number or e-mail address, the account shall be indefinitely suspended. Happiroo reserves the full discretion to suspend a user's account in the above event and does not have the liability to share any account information whatsoever. \n⦁\tWe may record your telephone calls to our call centres or to Us.  Termination or Suspension \n⦁\tYou agree that Happiroo may at any time terminate your access to the  App or Website or restrict or suspend your access to all or any part of the Website or the App at any time, for any or no reason, with or without prior notice, and without liability. \n⦁\tHappiroo shall be entitled at any time without giving any reason to terminate the booking of services done by You. Preservation / Disclosure \n⦁\tYou acknowledge, consent and agree that Happiroo may access, preserve and disclose your account information and content if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: \n⦁\tcomply with legal process nationally or internationally; \n⦁\tenforce these Terms of Use; \n⦁\trespond to claims that any Content violates the rights of third parties; \n⦁\trespond to your requests for customer service; \n⦁\tprotect the rights, property or personal safety of Happiroo, its subscribers and the public; or \n⦁\tpursuant to the terms of the Privacy Policy. Security Components \n⦁\tYou understand that our Website and  App and software embodied within the Website and  App may include security components that permit digital materials to be protected, and that use of these materials is subject to usage rules set by Happiroo and/or content providers who provide content to Happiroo. You may not attempt to override, disable, circumvent or otherwise interfere with any such security components and usage rules embedded in our platforms.  Happiroo and Third Parties \n⦁\tYou may be able to access links to third party sites from the  App or Website. Third parties could be advertisers, affiliate partners, strategic partners, or others. Happiroo expressly disclaims all responsibilities for such third party links. We do not warrant the products or offerings of, any of these businesses or individuals, or the accuracy of the content of their websites. Happiroo does not assume any responsibility or liability for the actions, product, and content of any such Third Party websites. Before you use any Third Party websites, you should review the applicable terms of use and policies for such Websites. If you decide to access any such linked Website, you do so at your own risk.  Compliance with Applicable Law \n⦁\tYou agree that You shall not use the  App and Website in order to host, display, upload, modify, publish, transmit, update, distribute, share, store or destroy material, including without limitation Happiroo Content: \n⦁\tin violation of any applicable law or regulation, \n⦁\tin a manner that will infringe the copyright, trademark, trade secret or other intellectual property or proprietary rights of others or violate the privacy, publicity or other personal rights of others, \n⦁\tthat belongs to another person and to which the user does not have any right to, \n⦁\tthat is grossly harmful, harassing, blasphemous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, pedophilic, libelous, invasive of another’s privacy, threatening, abusive or hateful or racially, ethnically objectionable, disparaging, relating encouraging money laundering or gambling or otherwise unlawful in any manner whatsoever, \n⦁\tharm minors in any way, \n⦁\tdeceives or misleads the addressee about the origin of such message or communicates any information which is grossly offensive or menacing in nature, \n⦁\timpersonate another person or entity, \n⦁\tcontains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of Happiroo’s computer systems or site or Happiroo’s users, customer’s computer systems or site, \n⦁\tthreatens the unity, integrity, defense, security or sovereignty of India, friendly relations with foreign states or of public order or causes incitement to the commission of any cognizable offence or prevents investigation of any offence or insulting any other nation. Intellectual Property Rights \n⦁\tThe  App and the Website are owned by Happiroo. Happiroo is the sole owner of the App, Website and all software created to provide You with the Services. Happiroo provides You with a single limited license to download, use and access the App/Website on Your mobile telephone devices for the limited purpose of using the Services. The license is specifically personal, non-transferable, and non-exclusive. All content on the App or the Website, which is including, but not limited to, designs, text, graphics, images, video, information, logos, button icons, software, audio files and any other content (“Content”) are the exclusive and sole property of Happiroo. You may not copy, reproduce or use such Content without due attribution of ownership to Happiroo. All icons and logos are trademarks of and proprietary to Happiroo. The unauthorized copying, modification, use or publication of these marks is strictly prohibited. \n⦁\tAll Content is the exclusive copyright of Happiroo or its licensors, except the Third Party Content and link to third party website. Systematic retrieval of Happiroo Content to create or compile, directly or indirectly, a collection, compilation, database or directory (whether through robots, spiders, automatic devices or manual processes) without written permission from Happiroo is prohibited. In addition, use of the Content for any purpose not expressly permitted by Happiroo in this Agreement is prohibited and may invite legal action. Disclaimer of Warranties and Liability All the material and products on our Website and  App, (including but not limited to software) and services, included on or otherwise made available to you through our Website and  App are provided on \"as is\" and \"as available\" basis without any representation or warranties, express or implied except otherwise specified in writing. Without prejudice to the forgoing paragraph, Happiroo does not warrant that: This Website will be constantly available, or available at all; or The information on this Website is complete, true, accurate or non-misleading; That the Services will meet the customer’s requirements. Happiroo will not be liable to you in any way or in relation to the Contents of, or use of, or otherwise in connection with its Website and  App. Happiroo does not warrant that this Website or the  App; information, Content, materials, product or services included on or otherwise made available to you through its Website and  App; the servers; or electronic communication sent from us are free of viruses or other harmful components. Happiroo shall not be liable for any conduct or behaviour or actions of service providers. However, Happiroo encourages you to notify us of any complaints that you may have against the service provider who has provided You with services on behalf of Happiroo. You agree and acknowledge that the use of the Services offered by Happiroo is at Your sole risk and that Happiroo "</string>
    <string name="cancellationPolicy"><![CDATA["You can cancel your order at any time after Booking Confirmation. Charges will be levied as mentioned below on cancellation of order:  \n1. No Charges will be levied if order cancellation requested \n2 hours before the starting of the service 2. 25% of the Booking Amount will be levied if order cancellation requested < 2 hours of the service time Refund will be processed immediately after Cancellations and can take up to 5-7 working days in reflecting in your account "]]></string>
    <string name="privacyPolicy">We reserve the right to request that you remove all links or any particular link to our Website. You approve to immediately remove all links to our Website upon request. We also reserve the right to amen these terms and conditions and it’s linking policy at any time. By continuously linking to our Website, you agree to be bound to and follow these linking terms and conditions.  Removal of links from our website If you find any link on our Website that is offensive for any reason, you are free to contact and inform us any moment. We will consider requests to remove links but we are not obligated to or so or to respond to you directly.  We do not ensure that the information on this website is correct, we do not warrant its completeness or accuracy; nor do we promise to ensure that the website remains available or that the material on the website is kept up to date.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">"To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we exclude all representations, warranties and conditions relating to our website and the use of this website. Nothing in this disclaimer will:   limit or exclude our or your liability for death or personal injury;  limit or exclude our or your liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation;  limit any of our or your liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law; or  exclude any of our or your liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law. The limitations and prohibitions of liability set in this Section and elsewhere in this disclaimer: (a) are subject to the preceding paragraph; and (b) govern all liabilities arising under the disclaimer, including liabilities arising in contract, in tort and for breach of statutory duty.  As long as the website and the information and services on the website are provided free of charge, we will not be liable for any loss or damage of any nature. "</string>
    <string name="customerSupport">Email- for customer care - happiroo.in@gmail.com          \nfor partner-happiroobusiness@gmail.com \nContact- 9999028002,9999762636  "</string>
</resources>
